chinaqualitycrafts.com 2017-12-23

# Privacy Policy of Our Site - About Us

**Introduction** ****

When you use our service, we may collect and use your related information. We hope that through the "privacy policy" , you may understand how do we collect, use, store this information , and how we can provide you with access, update, control, and protection of the information when you using our services. "privacy policy" is closely related to the services you use, please read it carefully so you can make an informed decision about using our platform. In order to fully understand the "privacy policy", ,we try to express more detailed information as follows.

 **Information Collecting** ****

When we provide services, we may collect, store and use personal information related to you. If you do not provide relevant information, you may not able to register as our users or can not enjoy some of the services we provide, or can not achieve the intended effect of the relevant services.

 **Information Providing** ****

When we provide services, we may collect, store and use personal information related to you. If you do not provide relevant information, you may not able to register as our users or can not enjoy some of the services we provide, or can not achieve the intended effect of the relevant services.

 **Information Using** ****

To provide you with our services;

When we provide services for authentication, customer service, security, fraud monitoring, archiving and backup purposes, to ensure that we provide you with the products and services security;

 **Information Sharing** ****

We may share your personal information

Used for the following purposes: 

\- To provide you with our services;; 

\- To achieve the purpose of "how we might use information";

\- To fulfill our obligations and to exercise our rights in the "service agreement" or the "privacy policy";

\- Understanding, maintaining and improving our services.
